testmyiq.net 2010-01-28

# mBill :: Privacy Statement

**PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY

mBill Privacy Policy

**

At mBill we respect and take steps to protect your privacy. We strive to make our site a safe environment for everyone who visits and uses mBill services. We are committed to providing you the best possible online service and experience as well as the best products and services. The purpose of this policy statement is to fully share with you:

| > | How we use the information  
---|---  
> | With whom we share the information  
> | How you can change the information  
  
This policy addresses our practices with respect to our website, but does not address the practices of any website we link to (including the merchants and content providers we link to). This policy is incorporated into, and subject to the terms of, our User Agreement.

_Information Collection_

mBill collects information through our web site at several points. We collect the following information about visitors for example personal contact details, business contact details business and banking details. We collect this information through the client information section and various other places. The information is given voluntarily. To receive our products and services, contact details are mandatory because ICSTIS requires it.

_How We Use Information Collected_

We use information which you provide us to keep track of the mBill services you have signed up to receive. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyse site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customise our site's content and layout. We do this in an attempt to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. We use your email address to contact you regarding administrative notices or latest news from time to time. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. If our policy on information collection or uses changes, will advise you by e-mail. 

_Protection of Database Information_

Any information sent to mBill for text messaging and or storage purposes will remain the property of the account holder. mBill will at no time collect or redistribute this information without your consent, except where legally required by law to do so. This is with particular reference to any database, numbers and/or recipient details that you may deliver to us, or store on our databases. mBill protects user information with security protocols, secure servers, SSL encryption and other technology and procedures used to protect consumer privacy.

_Disclosure of Your Information_

We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. We do aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. mBill offers features on our site where we will by necessity, need to provide some of your information to the third party offering such services. To the extent that that third party requires your information to enable you to use their service, we will notify you of the specific information that will be provided to such third parties. Before you use the service you should evaluate whether you will accept the terms and conditions of the third party service, and give mBill the right to pass your information on to that third party. In addition, we must comply with court orders, information requests from government agencies and regulators and other legal and regulatory processes that may require the disclosure of your personally-identifiable information.

_Problem Resolution_

If problems arise, users may contact mBill. We are committed to resolving disputes within a reasonable time frame.

**Frequently Asked Questions**

_Will you send advertising text messages to my cell phone, without my consent ?_  
No, we will not send you unwanted advertising text messages. We may initiate a program whereby we send advertising text messages to cell phones. However, this will be an opt-in based service. You will decide if, and when you want to receive advertising on your cell phone.

_I am getting spammed on my cell phone. What's happening?_  
One of the services, provided by mBill, allows visitors and members to send text messages to friends, family, colleagues, using the secure.mBill Interface. The secure.mBill Interface conditions of use forbid spamming to cell phone users and several software filters are in place to block spammers. However, we cannot guarantee that no spamming will ever occur.

_Reviewing/Changing Your Information_

If at any time you would like to change any information in your account, Login from the home page. Here you can change or update your information.

_Limits on Our Abilities_

Although your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal and technical environment, we cannot ensure that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties in ways not described in this policy. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to address or resolve inquiries or problems. This will not be done for commercial purposes or gain from mBill as such.

If you have further questions about our privacy policy or its implementation, please contact [info@mbill.net](mailto:info@mbill.net)

You acknowledge that acceptance of this privacy policy is a condition to your use of our services and you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions.
